艾娃  我想帮你
Ava, I want to help you.
她不需要你的帮助  我知道怎么救她
She doesn't need your help. I know how to save her.
是吗  怎么救
Oh, really? How?
珍妮特
Janet.
她这30年来
For the last 30 years,
都在量子域吸收量子能
she's been down there absorbing quantum energy.
我们可以提取那能量
We can extract that energy.
用它来修复艾娃的分子结构
We can use it to repair Ava's molecular structure...
提取
Extract it?
-是的  -你疯了吗
- Yes. - Are you insane?
那会把珍妮特撕裂的
That would rip Janet apart.
这你不能确定
You don't know that.
我要开启隧道
I'm gonna fire up your tunnel.
等珍妮特的位置出现在朗脑子里
When Janet's location pops into Lang's head,
他就得告诉我
he's gonna give it to me
否则我就把他交给联调局
or I'm gonna turn him over to the FBI.
什么
What?
你给我留在这里
You are gonna stay here
以防我需要你帮忙
just in case I need your help.